daemon-tools.cc 2016-12-02

# Privacy Policy - DAEMON-Tools.cc - DAEMON-Tools.cc

## Privacy Policy

At Disc Soft, your security and privacy is of the utmost importance to us. So we’ve developed a Privacy Policy that covers how we collect, use, disclose, and store your information. Please let us know if you have any questions.

### Collection and Use of Personal Information

Personal information is data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact a single person.

### What personal information we collect

When you register your account, purchase a product, we may collect your email address and contact information.

### How we use your personal information

The personal information we collect allows us to register and identify your software product license. It also allows us to keep you posted on Disc Soft latest product announcements, software updates, and upcoming events. If you don’t want to be on our mailing list, you can opt out anytime by updating [your preferences](https://www.daemon-tools.cc/account/options).

### Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information

We also collect non-personal information − data in a form that does not permit direct association with any specific individual.

Disc Soft collects general demographic information about visitors to our websites. The information we collect creates a broad picture of our population rather than focusing on any one individual. This information is used to continually refine our products and to identify the most popular areas of our websites.

### Cookies and Other Technologies

Disc Soft uses third-party advertising company (Google) to serve ads when you visit our web site. This company uses [DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by this company, click [here](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

### Disclosure to Third Parties

The personal information will not be shared with Disc Soft partners or any third parties. It is stored on Disc Soft computers and accessed by authorized Disc Soft personnel only.

Disc Soft will not share non-personal information associated with your use with any third parties unless we   
(i) have your consent;  
(ii) conclude that it is required by law or has a good faith belief that access, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of Disc Soft, software product, its users or the public; or  
(iii) provide such information in certain limited circumstances to third parties to carry out tasks on Disc Soft behalf (e.g., data storage) with strict limitations that prevent the data from being used or shared except as directed by Disc Soft. When this is done, it is subject to agreements that oblige those parties to process such information only on Disc Soft instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

### Protection of Personal Information

Disc Soft online services use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on all web pages where personal information is collected. To make purchases from these services, you must use an SSL-enabled browser. Doing so protects the confidentiality of your personal information while it’s transmitted over the Internet.

### Privacy Questions

Disc Soft may update its Privacy Policy from time to time. If you have any questions or concerns about Privacy Policy or data processing, please contact us.

Last updated: September 10, 2013

Disc Soft Ltd.  
P.O. Box 2284  
16 Albert Hoy Avenue, Belama Phase 1  
Belize City, Belize C.A.
